Guide to the Doris Duke Audiovisual Collection, 1919-2012 and undated RL.10005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audio, 1923-1989
  - Phonodiscs, 1934-1989; 198 items
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0014_Unknown_CTOP14_01; RL10005-PD-0014_Unknown_CTOP14_02)
      First track includes two songs. Both are unknown but sound like traditional Hawaiian music with singers accompanied by slide guitar and ukulele. Second track also includes two songs, again traditional Hawaiian music with singers accompanied by slide guitar and ukulele.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0014)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0015_Unknown_CTOP16_01_02; RL10005-PD-0015_Unknown_CTOP16_02_02)
      Both tracks consist of tests of live tracks and tracks of other songs. Most songs are unrecognizable as they are abruptly cut off.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0015)
    - Beamer at the Piano, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0016_Unknown_CTOP17_1_01; RL10005-PD-0016_Unknown_CTOP17_1_02)
      First track is piano solo, song unknown but has a fast, boogie-woogie beat. Second track also piano solo; song unknown but is a slower melody. Song ends abruptly when a woman (presumably Doris Duke) starts talking in the background. Third track also slower piano solo; song unknown. Also ends abruptly.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0016)
    - Beamer at the Piano, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0017_Unknown_CTOP17_2_01; RL10005-PD-0017_Unknown_CTOP17_2_02)
      First track is a man speaking about how fear is destructive to peace (approximately 1 minute). This transitions into the second track which is a somber piano solo, song unknown. This cuts off abruptly and leads into another piano solo; song unknown but more upbeat, jazzy tune. The last track is a piano solo "I Can't Give You Anything But Love" which leads into "It Had To Be You".Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0017)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0018_Unknown_URSOriginal1_01)
      Sound like a practice session on piano and includes scales, chords, and bits of various songs. Artist unknown, but could be Doris Duke.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0018)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0019_Unknown_URSOriginal2_01; RL10005-PD-0019_Unknown_URSOriginal2_02)
      First track has approximately 6 minutes of dead air; remaining 30 seconds sounds like a piano practice session, artist unknown. Track 2 has approximately 5:45 of dead air, then man says "Testing" and piano solo begins. Song and artist unknown, can hear pages turning in the background.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0019)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0020_Unknown_URSOriginal3_01; RL10005-PD-0020_Unknown_URSOriginal3_02)
      In the first track a door closes and a piano solo begins; song is "I Can't Give You Anything But Love" and artist is likely Doris Duke. Recording is slightly distorted. Second track is same song. Track 3 is also a piano solo; song is unknown but person (presumably Doris Duke) playing piano periodically whistles along with song. End of this track lead into next track where again piano solo, but song unknown. Man then says "Hello, hello" and then unknown artist plays "A Pretty Girl is Like a Melody" on piano.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0020)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0021_Unknown_URSOriginal4_01; RL10005-PD-0021_Unknown_URSOriginal4_02)
      First track begins with man saying "Hello everybody, how are you? Everybody hello." Unknown woman accompanied by guitar(?) sings "Old Faithful". After song ends, same woman says "Well people, I don't know if any of you folks have heard this song but its adapted from Rudyard Kipling's 'I've Learned About Women from Her". Here it is, such as it is." Ends abruptly mid-song. This song continues on second side of phonograph. This song also ends when someone knocks on the doo and the woman singing asks "Yes?"Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0021)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0022_Unknown_URSOriginal5_01; RL10005-PD-0022_Unknown_URSOriginal5_02)
      First track begins with man announcing "Introducing Miss (?) Ying who is playing to you through the courtesy of Mr. Cull, proprietor of the Do Yung restaurant in Hong Kong. Go ahead." Woman sings song in Chinese (?) accompanied by a string instrument. Track 2 begins with man announcing "This is Ah King(?) sing and playing in Hong Kong." Same woman as in first track sings song accompanied by instrument.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0022)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0023_Unknown_URSOriginal6_01)
      Unknown male sings "Falling in Love with Love" accompanied by piano. Song ends and a woman laughs in the background.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0023)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0024_Unknown_URSOriginal7_01)
      First track is unknown woman singing "I Want to Be Loved" accompanied by piano.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0024)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0025_Unknown_URSOriginal8_01; RL10005-PD-0025_Unknown_URSOriginal8_02)
      Both sides consist of recordings of radio broadcasts, with a mixture of music and commentary. All recordings begin and end abruptly. One recording is from KFLP in Australia where the broadcaster announces he will speak of "Peace Amongst the Nations Around the World."Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0025)
    - Joe Castro Trio. This Can't Be Love/I've Got the World on a String., undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0026_This_Cant_Ive_Got_01; RL10005-PD-0026_This_Cant_Ive_Got_02)
      Both songs instrumental only; includes piano, bass and drums. Very "jazzy" versions of songs.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0026)
    - Polymon Bongo, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0040_Polymon_Bongo_01)
      Unknown woman singing "Polymon Bongo" accompanied by piano throughout, joined by drums at the end of song.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0040)
    - Railroad Yoke Highball [?] / [illegible handwriting looks like "Dernier"], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0041_Railroad_Yoke_Denison_01; RL10005-PD-0041_Railroad_Yoke_Denison_02)
      Both tracks consist of various duck calls. Before each call an unknown man announces the name of the duck call.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0041)
    - Soltis a Virginia, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0042_Soltis_Unknown_7305_01; RL10005-PD-0042_Soltis_Unknown_7305_02)
      First track is unknown woman (Virginia Hays?) singing "Ain't Misbehavin'" accompanied by piano. Second track is same woman singing "Can't Take That Away From Me" accompanied by piano.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0042)
    - Doris / [Leta?]. Must Have That Man / [Say], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0043_Must_Have_That_Man_Say_01; RL10005-PD-0043_Must_Have_That_Man_Say_02)
      First track opens with two women talking (unintelligible) and then lead into recording. Track is presumably Doris Duke playing piano and singing "Must Have That Man". Second track is presumably Leta [McBean] singing "Say What You Mean To Say" accompanied by piano (played by Doris Duke?)Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0043)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0044_Unknown_X2_01)
      Track opens with woman asking "Can you hear me?" Then unknown man (identifies himself as "Goldberg") describes the scene and the people sitting around (can hear people talking in background), including Doris [Duke], Mary Sampson(?), Vera, McIntosh Alley(?). Goldberg then "signs off".Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0044)
    - Jack. Dangerous / Sweetest Thing, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0045_Dangerous_Sweetest_Thing_01; RL10005-PD-0045_Dangerous_Sweetest_Thing_02)
      First track is Jack singing "Dangerous" accompanied by piano. Second track is Jack singing "Sweetest Thing" accompanied by piano.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0045)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0046_Unknown_X4_01; RL10005-PD-0046_Unknown_X4_02)
      First track is unknown pianist playing unknown song. Very bad recording - barely audible. Second track is presumably Doris Duke playing piano and singing "It Is Better To Be By Yourself". Recording ends abruptly.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0046)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0047_Unknown_X5_01)
      Track is presumably Doris Duke playing piano and singing "Come Rain or Come Shine". Piano ends about two-thirds way through and just Doris singing. Song ends abruptly.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0047)
    - Doris / [Leta?]. It Had to Be You / You Go To My Head, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0048_Had_to_Be_Went_to_My_Head_01; RL10005-PD-0048_Had_to_Be_Went_to_My_Head_02)
      Track one is Doris playing and singing "It Had to Be You". At end of song she comments "this one is really ripe". Second track is Leta singing "You Go To My Head" accompanied by piano (Doris playing?).Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0048)
    - Doris. Taking a Chance / Where Are You, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0049_Taking_Chance_Where_Are_01; RL10005-PD-0049_Taking_Chance_Where_Are_02)
      First track opens with unknown man saying "Don't be alarmed". Then Doris playing piano and singing "Taking a Chance On Love". Second track is Doris and another woman singing "I Guess I'll Have to Change My Plans". Last track is Doris playing and singing "Where You Are".Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0049)
    - Doris / Jack. It was / It [had?], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0050_It_Was_It_Had_01; RL10005-PD-0050_It_Was_It_Had_02)
      Track one opens with Doris playing piano and unknown person whistling (Jack?) and woman (Doris?) humming along. Then Doris sings "It Had to Be You". Second track almost identical, but Jack sings and hums "It Had to Be You". Assume Doris is playing piano.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0050)
    - Doris? Embrace Me / [Same?], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0051_Embrace_Me_1_2_01; RL10005-PD-0051_Embrace_Me_1_2_02)
      First track is unknown woman (Liz?) accompanied by piano singing "Embraceable You". Second track is same woman accompanied by piano singing same song albeit a slightly different rendition.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0051)
    - [Marian?] / Doris. I Follow / Some Day, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0052_I_Follow_Women_Same_Day_01; RL10005-PD-0052_I_Follow_Women_Same_Day_02)
      Track one is unknown woman (Marian Paschal?) accompanied by piano singing "I'll Follow My Heart". Song ends and same woman says "Oh, listen, don't play it back, it's so flat, really. No it isn't, it's terrible." Track 2 is Doris Duke playing piano and singing "Someday Sweetheart". At end of song she calls the song a "stinkaroo".Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0052)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0053_Unknown_X16_01; RL10005-PD-0053_Unknown_X16_02)
      Track one begins with piano solo (pianist unknown) then unknown woman sings "And Russia is Her Name". Track two is a woman giving singing instructions (i.e., tone, scales, etc.) accompanied by piano.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0053)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0054_Unknown_X17_01; RL10005-PD-0054_Unknown_X17_02)
      Track one is unknown woman? accompanied by piano singing unknown song. Song ends and same woman? sings the same song. Track 3 unknown woman accompanied by piano singing "Come Rain or Come Shine". Song abruptly ends. Side 2 is recorded on but only machine noise.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0054)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0055_Unknown_X18_01; RL10005-PD-0055_Unknown_X18_02)
      Both tracks are unknown woman singing "That's the Beginning of the End" accompanied by piano. Second track is not as good as recording as the first.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0055)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0056_Unknown_X19_01; RL10005-PD-0056_Unknown_X19_02)
      At the beginning of track one a door closes. Presumably Doris Duke practicing piano; song is unknown. Second track is a "skit" performed by Doris, Mary, Laddie, and Eddie. Doris is clearly identifiable in the skit.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0056)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0057_Unknown_X20_01; RL10005-PD-0057_Unknown_X20_02)
      The first track has a few faint voices talking. It sounds like they are testing out the recording equipment. Second track is a pianist (presumably Doris Duke) playing the same song as in RL10005-PD-0056) except that she is whistling along with song.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0057)
    - [Part I - Men and Money], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0058_Unknown_X21_01; RL10005-PD-0058_Unknown_X21_02)
      Tracks one and two are presumably narration of Part I of "Men and Money". Man (James Cromwell?) speaks about unemployment as it relates to ware, politics, economics, and system of distribution amongst other topics.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0058)
    - Part II - Men and Money, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0059_Unknown_X22_01; RL10005-PD-0059_Unknown_X22_02)
      Tracks one and two are presumably narration of Part II of "Men and Money". Man (James Cromwell?) speaks about facing a "new" world and potential of national power/industrialization. Vital problem lies in system of distribution.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0059)
    - Sol Hoopie, Phil Hess. Aloha Nui Loa - To Doris Duke, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0060_Aloha_Nui_Loa_01; RL10005-PD-0060_Aloha_Nui_Loa_02)
      First track begins with man saying "Aloha, Lahi Lahi. This is Sol Ho'opi'i. We are dedicating this number, Phil (?) and I to Lahi Lahi, Doris Duke Cromwell beautiful lady of Hawaii. Sol(?) playing steel guitar and singing unknown Hawaiian song accompanied by piano. Second track begins with Sol saying "Aloha, Lahi Lahi. I just had to play this number for you. I'm dedicating this number to you, 'He's The Healer of Broken Hearts'." Sol sings accompanied by steel guitar and piano.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0060)
    - [Part III - Men and Money], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0063_Unknown_X11_01; RL10005-PD-0063_Unknown_X11_02)
      Tracks one and two are presumably narration of Part III of "Men and Money". Man (James Cromwell?) speaks solving economic problems in the "great American way". Speaks about ways to solve economic problems via money and the way it's used and regulated.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0063)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0064_Unknown_X12_01; RL10005-PD-0064_Unknown_X12_02)
      Side 2 of album sounds like the continuation of "Men and Money." On Side 1 the first track sounds like the ending of "Men and Money" (approximately 1 minute). The second and third tracks is unknown woman singing unknown songs accompanied by piano. Last track is same woman presumably reading an advertisement for a new type of bathing suit. She laughs at end.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0064)
    - Questions and Answers / Questions and Answers, Leta Byrnes [illegible], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0065_Unknown_X13_01; RL10005-PD-0065_Unknown_X13_02)
      Both sides are a series of questions and answers (not serious) asked to different members of the group (i.e., "How much do you calculate all your women have cost you?") Group includes James and Doris Duke Cromwell, John and Leta McDonald, Mr. Brad(?), and Mr. and Mrs. Rexford (?).Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0065)
    - [Men and Money], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0066_Unknown_X14_01; RL10005-PD-0066_Unknown_X14_02)
      Tracks one and two are presumably narration of another part of "Men and Money". Man (James Cromwell?) speaks primarily about the worldwide movement of Social Security and then about Communism.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 17, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0066)
    - [Men and Money], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0067_Unknown_X15_01; RL10005-PD-0067_Unknown_X15_02)
      Both tracks sound similar to the tracks on RL10005-PD-0059. Possible re-recording?Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 17, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0067)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0068_Aninale_J3a_Unknown_J3b_01; RL10005-PD-0068_Aninale_J3a_Unknown_J3b_02)
      Track one is unknown woman (Virginia?) singing "How Deep is the Ocean?" accompanied by piano. Second track is same woman singing "Happiness is a Thing Called Joe" also accompanied by piano.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 17, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0068)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0069_Unknown_J4_01; RL10005-PD-0069_Unknown_J4_02)
      Both tracks are Doris Duke playing piano and singing "Can't Help Lovin' that Man of Mine". Second recording is a better recording.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 17, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0069)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0070_Unknown_J5_01; RL10005-PD-0070_Unknown_J5_02)
      All three tracks are Doris Duke singing and playing piano. Songs include "Too Marvelous for Words", "(I'm) Confessin' (that I Love You)", and "I've Got a Right to Sing the Blues".Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Phonodisc (Box 17, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0070)
    - Happiness is Just a Thing Called Joe/How Deep Is the Ocean?, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0071_Happiness_Is_How_Deep_01; RL10005-PD-0071_Happiness_Is_How_Deep_02)
      Sounds similar to recording RL10005-PD-0068, except not as good as recording due to issues with the album.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Phonodisc (Box 17, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0071)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0072_Unknown_T1_01; RL10005-PD-0072_Unknown_T1_02)
      Side 1 is essentially blank and has intermittent hum and faint sounds. Side 2 is also essentially blank with intermittent hum and faint sounds.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 17, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0072)
    - Phaedra. Up Against the Wall, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 17, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0080)
    - James Cleveland with the Angelic Choir. Volume 6 "The Grace of God", undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 18, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0084)
    - James Cleveland with the Angelic Choir. Volume 8 - Part 2, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 18, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0086)
    - James Cleveland with the Angelic Choir. Volume 9, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 18, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0087)
    - James Cleveland and the Cleveland Singers. He Leadeth Me., undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 18, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0089)
    - Rev. Joseph D. Linton and the Progressive Baptist Church Choir of St. Louis, Missouri. Rain Down Fire., undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 18, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0092)
    - Rev. Lawrence Roberts Directs the Angelic Choir. "The Girl Who Loved Jesus" (I Love Jesus), undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0095)